

PERSONAL PROFILE

Computer Engineer, passionate about technology, with experience in personal treatment and technical support. Interested in working in the area of Information Technology mainly in the area of Networks and Security as well as in programming.

CONTACT

- Tlalnepantla, Edo. Méx
- carlospardo1411@gmail.com
- 5569317662

EDUCATION

Universidad Nacional Autónoma de México. Ingeniería en Computación. 2014- 2021

CARLOS PARDO

COMPUTER ENGINEER

SKILLS

- Successful working in a team environment, as well as independently.
- The ability to work under pressure
- Customer service and support.
- Linux, Networks, Git.
- Front End Development (HTML/CSS/JS)
- NodeJS, Firebase, MongoDB

WORK EXPERIENCE

Help Desk at Afore XXI Banorte.

DECEMBER 2018-MAY 2019

Responsibilities:

- Physical and software examination to mobile devices (Tablets).
- Physical review and if possible repair of fingerprint reader devices.
- Administration of mobile devices.
- End users support.
- Attention to suppliers.

Help Desk internship at Robert Bosch Mexico.

JUNE 2019-OCTOBER 2019

Responsibilities:

- End users support on-site or remotely.
- Computer equipment management
- Installation, update and repair of Software and Operating Systems.
- Attention to suppliers.

Technical Support & Web Development at Digital Logic.

OCTOBER 2019-APRIL 2021

Responsibilities:

- On site or remote support related to Vizrt Software
- Computer equipment management
- Installation, update and repair of Software and Operating Systems.
- Software, scripts and web development.